All right, so in this section, we've made our network more efficient.
好 在这部分 我们提高了网络的效率
We've done this by getting rid of the multiplication by 1 because we don't
通过去掉 * 1 提高了效率 因为根本不需要乘
need to, because it doesn't change anything.
它不会带来任何改变
And we've gotten rid of the processing of any of the words that have 0 in
而且 我们也去掉了对所有对含 0 单词的
them altogether.
处理步骤
And this really should increase the speed of both the training and
这大大提高了我们网络的训练速度
the testing of our network, and the running of our network,
和测试速度 运行速度
by a significant amount, which we'll find out in a second.
我们一会儿就会看到
Now, in order to make this change,
那么 为了实现这部分修改
notice this top part of this class didn't really change, right?
请注意 这个类最前面的部分并没有变化 对吧？
So we still initialize the network, we still create the wave matrix,
所以我们依然初始化网络 依然创建同样的权重矩阵
still create the same word index lookup.
创建相同的单词索引查找表
I left these methods around but we're not going to use them.
这些方法我都写了 但这里不会使用它们
And then we get to these train methods and things really start to change.
来到训练方法部分了 这才是改变真正开始的地方
So I added kind of a pre processing step to the train method,
我在训练方法中添加了一个预处理步骤
which was the following.
就是下面这些：
It takes each of the kind of training_reviews_raw, so
它取 training_reviews_raw 里的每条评论
that the raw text, and it creates a set of indices.
也就是原始文本 然后创建一组索引
So it converts all the words to numbers, right?
因此 它将所有单词转换成数字了 对吧？
But to the rows that they're corresponding to.
也就是它们对应的行
So in this case it's like what we did up here with this 4 and 9, right?
就像上面这里的 4 和 9 一样
So then we had this list of indices and we can just sum them into this vector.
我们就得到了这个索引列表 可以将它们加到这个向量中
And this ends up being really, really fast, which is great.
最终 这个网络会变得非常非常快 这很好
So what we did here is just a kind of a bigger version of that,
所以 我们在这里所做的 就像是上面步骤的放大版
where for each review we convert the words to the row
对于每条评论 我们将单词转换成它们在
of our weight matrix that it corresponds to, right?
权重矩阵中对应的行
So our inputs correspond to rows in the matrix and
所以我们的输入对应于矩阵中的行
our outputs correspond to columns, right?
而输出对应于列 对吧？
So in major matrix multiplication is kind of how it works out.
这就是在主矩阵中对乘法的处理
And that allows us to make it down here to completely skip generating our input
这使我们可以在这里完全跳过创建
vector, right?
输入向量
So we don't have to do that in forward propagation at all.
我们在正向传播中完全可以省略这一步
We jump straight to generating our hidden layer.
而是直接跳到创建隐藏层
All we do is we iterate through each index in our review, each index,
我们所做的 就是遍历评论中的每个索引
and we sum that row of weights_0_1 into layer_1, right?
然后将 weights_0_1 这行加到 layer_1
So we take their 1, which has been emptied out right here,
我们取 layer_1 我们已在这里清空了它
and we say all right, for each row in weights_0_1, add it into layer_1.
然后 对于 weights_0_1 中的每个行 将它添加到 layer_1
What we're doing is we're saying for each row, add it into thin layer.
我们所做的就是 对于每个行 将它添加到这些层
So add the row for horrible, it's this one, add the row for terrible,
所以 添加 horrible 的行 它是这个 添加 terrible 的行
it's this one, add it in here, right?
这里这个 将它添加到这里
We're skipping this entirely and
我们完全跳过了这个 (excellent) 以及
the 70,000 other words that were mentioned here.
这里提到的其他 70,000 多个单词
That is a huge, huge time saving and
这节省了大量的时间
I think I'm really excited to see how much speed that gives it.
我真的很期望看到它的速度提升到多少
Now this part's exactly the same, Layer_2 error is exactly the same,
那么 这部分是完全一样的 layer_2_error 完全一样
Layer_2_delta is exactly the same.
layer_2_delta 也是一样
Layer_1 error and 1_delta are exactly the same, because nothing's changed.
layer_1 error 和 1_delta 也完全一样 因为什么都没改变
The only thing that's different now is the way that we update
唯一不同的一点是 我们更新权值的方式
the weights is basically just the inverse of when we populated it.
它基本与我们填充它的方式相反
So we iterate through the same indices and we say all right,
那么我们遍历相同的索引 然后说
we're just going to update the ones that we forward propagated,
我们只更新那些正向传播的值
the ones that we used and we're going to leave all the rest of them alone.
我们使用过的那些值 所有其他的值都不管
This actually makes even more sense when you look at how
当你看看反向传播如何发生的
back propagation happened or how this happens, right?
或者如何发生的 这就显得更有道理了
So when you're computing this final, that's not a weight delta, your weight
当你计算这个最终 weight_delta 你的权重调整数值
adjustment, you're multiplying the input value by the delta that's here.
你用输入值乘以这里的增量
So we have back propagate delta, you have delta on hidden layer.
反向传播增量 隐藏层中的增量
So the way to update these four indices, you say 1 times the delta that's
那么 更新这四个索引的方式 是用 1 乘以这里的增量
right here, and you subtract that from these weights.
然后从这些权值中减去乘积
Now the thing is if it's a 0, that subtraction's always going to be 0.
现在的问题是 如果这个是 0 那么减的永远都是 0
So we can skip that on the way back as well, which is great.
所以我们也可以跳过它 非常好
So that's how we do our weight update.
这就是我们更新权值的方式
All the evaluation logic is the same, the test logic is the same,
所有的评估逻辑都是一样的 测试逻辑也是一样的
the run logic is the same.
运行逻辑也一样
And now we want to try it out.
现在我们来试试看
So we're going to go ahead and grab our in the network, put it right there.
我们从上面抓取 SentimentNetwork 将它放在这里
Then we're going to grab the actual training, so just a reference, right?
然后抓取实际的训练 只是一个参考
This train did around a 100 reviews per second.
这个训练每秒处理约 100 条评论
Go ahead and run that, put that right there, grab the test.
将它放在这里 然后抓取测试
I guess they're going to train, grab the test,
我觉得训练速度应该是……
I guess we kind of want to see that, so I'll see if I can.
我们应该会看到 我找找看
A 1000 reviews a second, it's ten times faster, over ten times,
每秒 1000 个评论 这是之前的十倍 超过十倍了
look at that 1300 and still training at the same conversion speed.
看看 接近 1300 个 仍然在以相同的转换速度训练
Look at that, 1300 reviews per second, that is over and order of magnitude
看看 每秒 1300 个评论 速度提高了一个数量集多
increase in speed, because we got rid of all these problems, like COC testing.
因为我们摆脱了所有问题 像 COC 测试
Okay testing, you almost didn't even noticed it happened.
说到测试 你几乎没注意到它有什么变化
Cool, awesome.
非常棒
And we're getting a great score, actually, yeah, yeah.
而且我们的得分也不错
I mean it should be exactly identical, right?
我是说它应该完全一样 对吧？
because nothing has changed.
因为什么都没有改变
Man, this is great, that's so much faster, awesome.
太棒了 这下快多了
So this is great.
非常棒
If we wanted to, we could train multiple iterations, right?
如果我们想 我们可以训练多次迭代 对吧？
So if I said times 2.
比如我说乘以 2
So we'll hit train and the second it starts, so
我们点击训练 开始后
it's converting everything into indices right now.
它会将所有的东西转换为索引
And then it's going to start training, so
然后开始训练
I guess maybe I lost a little bit here.
这里好像有点不清楚
But if you're going to keep doing more iterations,
但是如果你继续进行更多的迭代
it's going to use the same indices.
它将使用相同的索引
So it converts the indices once, keeps going.
它只需转换一次索引
Wow, reviews per second it's getting up to 1500, it's crazy fast.
哇塞 每秒评论数接近 1500 这非常快了
So we can keep training, training accuracy keeps going up.
我们可以继续训练 训练准确度继续提高
It's just the faster your network goes,
网络的速度越高
the more iterations you can do in a given period of time, right?
在给定时间段内你就能做更多迭代 对吧？
And the way that we're able to accomplish this is by just stripping out
那么我们做到这一切的方法是清除掉那些
the stuff that the neural net is doing that actually isn't helping us predict
神经网络所做的但不能提高预测或者学习效果的
or really even to learn.
操作步骤
That's really what the strategy is all about, so yeah.
这就是我们真正的策略
Now, in the next section we're going to kind of go back to our data and
那么 在下一部分 我们将回到数据上
say okay, can we kind of improve the modeling?
看看 我们能否改进模型？
And so we improved the way that we frame the problem.
我们改进了问题的架构方式
Do we improve the way that the neural net is for
是否因为我们训练的方法得当
back propagation because of how we train a problem?
改进了神经网络的正向和反向传播？
So because we set up just pushing forward the vocabulary, this allowed us
由于我们的设置中 只将词汇表向前传递
to trim out a lot of inefficient waste that the neural net was computing.
这去除了神经网络中的很多低效率的计算浪费
And now we're going to go back.
现在 我们要返回去
Okay, can we reframe the problem again to reduce even more noise and
看我们是否可以再次重构这个问题 进一步减少噪音
potentially even reduce more weight propagations we have to do,
并且减少更多的权值传播
to speed how fast it learns and actually how fast it computes?
以加快学习速度和实际的计算速度？
So we're going to do one more iteration of this in project six.
所以我们将在项目六中再做一次迭代
I'll see you there.
到时候见